(Amy(in flashback):)Darn it.
(Amy(in flashback):)There's something
in my eye,
(Amy(in flashback):)and I need to sort
these coins by size.
(Amy(in flashback):)Can you help?
(Amy(in flashback):)Penny?
(Amy(in flashback):)I really want to
eat this banana,
(Amy(in flashback):)but it's stuck inside
this bamboo puzzle box.
Son of a bitch!
(Sheldon:)Okay, that's great.
(Sheldon:)Now, let it go.
(Penny:)I can't believe you were
testing me against a chimp!
(Sheldon:)Well, excuse me,
Amy was testing you.
(Sheldon:)I was rooting for you.
(Sheldon:)Good job on that banana box,
by the way.
(Sheldon:)Why would she
even do this?
(Sheldon:)She's been conducting
an experiment on apes
(Sheldon:)where they're given
various puzzles to solve.
(Sheldon:)I was surprised
at the complexity of the puzzles
(Sheldon:)and thought some humans wouldn't
be able to solve them.